{
    "id": "f7bc3e4c91d944db9a5d4da6fec45125",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………………. you were hungry, why didn’t you tell me?",
            "description": "If expresses a condition",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Whether",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6af20167f7d7459c9f6ee0c9e7e9f4ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. they were resting after work, I couldn’t talk to them.",
            "description": "As gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "As",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "229308ae1826407582299bb84b20637c"
        },
        {
            "question": "What will you do …………………………. you lose your job?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "if",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "38a8c85b30774a0c949eebe0eea777ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… he could not meet the deadline, he was told to leave.",
            "description": "As gives the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "As",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2be4323cc3734e5686e79ed704a6788f"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. I tried hard, I could not open the door.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "33bc394297f44d149ed29a60d94cd378"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… I knew no one at the party, I had a nice time.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "As",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a56e43e4a45c4b1abde143f2e7b21d6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………. a terrorist or a spy.",
            "description": "Either means one or the other.",
            "answers": [
                "Either",
                "Neither",
                "Both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "98339c149f5549aa90bf8209a3c0a9f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was laid to rest in the town …………………….. he spent much of his life.",
            "description": "Where can mean in which.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "there",
                "here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7a625a49bc054dd0ae0dfe03f1a478ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. you are dishonest, no one will trust you.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition and as gives the reason. Either could be used here with slightly different meanings. ",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "As",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f26dc6f054a14737af4e9011589640ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "I called her again and again …………………….. she didn’t pick up my phone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1dad5bfbd1124889bbc915510c5da65b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will give him the message …………………….. he arrives.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as soon as",
                "as long as",
                "as fast as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "587ea7feef0c4e9ba673847fbcc09d1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. she is a rich heiress, she is very humble.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "As",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7838f997492142ae90b7c63100c3aabe"
        }
    ]
}